CHARLEE DOLOR

Address: Calamba, City Phone: 09666807016

Email: dolorcharlee55@gmail.com

SUMMARY

I am a graduating IT student with a strong foundation in backend development and programming. Experienced working in an IT company as backend developer as part of on-the-job training. Can work well both in a team and individually.

WORK EXPERIENCE

SHS OJT Trainee Jan 2020 - Feb 2020

Install windows operating system to a computer

- Assembling PCs
- · Basic computer troubleshooting
- · Using AutoCAD for creating 2D and 3D models

Backend Developer (OJT Practicum - IT)

Feb 2024 - May 2024

- · Created RESTful API using PHP
- · Used Insomnia as API client
- · Codeception and PHPUnit for unit testing
- · Led a team of 8 to deliver a project on time

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

Aug 2020 - Jul 2024

University of Cabuyao (Pamantasan ng Cabuyao)

 Thesis on "Gate Security and Monitoring System Using Face Recognition and Image Processing Techniques".

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Technical Skills: Software Development (C#, Java, Python), Backend Web Development (PHP & Laravel), Programming, MySQL, SQL Query, Document Processing (Excel, Word, PowerPoint)
- · Languages: English, Filipino
- Certifications: Competency in Backend Web Development